Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Music, 1917-1984; Series 5.
  - Published, Subseries 2.; 117 items
    - Walk on water, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - What do the simple folk do?, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - When you're smiling, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Why don't you believe me?, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Will it go 'round in circles, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Wishin', 1951 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Wonder of you, the, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Yester-me, yester-you, yesterday, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Zingara (gypsy), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - 1980, 1979; copies (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea, 1931 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Didn't You Know (You'd Have to Cry Sometime), 1969; photocopy (Box 80, Folder 5)
      Plate no.: Y0315-2
      Also written by Valerie Simpson.
    - The Look Of Love, 1967; piano and voice (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Border Gate at Tijuana, Ozalid print of part (unspecified instrumentation) (Box 77, Folder 5)
      From the Warner Bros.-Seven Arts picture "Petulia."
    - El Bimbo, trumpet, rhythm; manuscript parts (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - The Old Piano Roll Blues, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - The Little Drummer Boy, 1958; piano and voice (Box 157, Folder 11)
      Words and music also written by: Henry Onorati, and Harry Simeone.
    - Pretend, 1952; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 20)
      Also written by: Cliff Parman, and Frank Lavere.
    - Driving Fuji Tecque, 1966; drums, trumpet, guitar; ozalid print (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Every Boy, 1963; manuscript with lyrics (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Fly Me to the Moon, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Don't Let Me Lose This dream, 1967; Ozalid manuscript and copies (Box 80, Folder 12)
      Also written by Ted White.
    - Theme from "Brannigan", 1975; Ozalid print of part (unspecified instrumentation) (Box 77, Folder 8)
      From the United Artists motion picture, "Brannigan."
    - Baby, I'm for Real, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      Also written by Anna Gaye.
    - The Girl from Ipanema (Box 81, Folder 21)
      Lyrics also written by: Norman Gimbel.
    - Gonna Give Her All the Love I've got, 1967; published piano reduction (Box 82, Folder 5)
      Also written by: Norman Whitfield.
    - Green-Eyed Lady, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      Plate no.: 721
      Also written by: J.C. Phillips, and David Riordan.
    - Greenback Dollar (Box 82, Folder 12)
      Plate no.: PV1023
      Also written by: Ken Ramsey.
    - Mame, tpt; tbn; rhy; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - He's Got the Whole World in His Hands, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Eu te Amo, Amor (I Love You, My Love), 1968; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Abraham, Martin and John, 1968; copy (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - How Can I Forget, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 26)
      Lyrics and music also by: Norman Whitfield.
    - How Insensitive (Box 83, Folder 29)
      Lyrics also by: Norman Gimbel.
    - I Can't Give You Anything But Love, 1928 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - I Don't Know Why, 1931 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - I Surrender, Dear, 1931 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - I Want My Mama, 1939 (Box 84, Folder 27)
      Spanish lyrics by George Negrette. Also written by: Vincente Paiva.
    - I Wouldn't Change the Man He Is, 1968; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 1)
      Also written by Valerie Simpson. Photocopy.
    - I Will Wait for You, 1964; piano, voice, lead sheet, tenor saxophone, clarinet, baritone saxophone, trombone; ozalids, manuscript parts, copies (Box 85, Folder 14)
      All parts other than the piano/vocal part are unpublished.
    - Ich Tough, 1966; trumpets (2), trombone, guitars, drums; ozalid prints of parts (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - If I Ever Lose This Heaven, 1973; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - If You Don't, 1964; lead sheet; ozalid copy (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - If You Walked Away, 1973; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - If You Want My Lovin', 1961; lead sheet; ozalid copy (Box 85, Folder 8)
      Words and music also by: Scott Turner.
    - I'll Have the Last Waltz with Mother, 1931; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 12)
      Also written by: Charles Tobias, and George J. Bennett. Photocopy.
    - I'll Keep the Lovelight Burning, 1942; piano and voice (Box 85, Folder 13)
      Also written by: Nick Kenny, and Harold Levy. Photocopy.
    - I'm Afraid the Masquerade is Over, 1938; piano and voice (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - I'm Dreaming, 1975; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 16)
      Words and music also by: Gary Osborne.
    - In God We Trust, 1943; piano and voice (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - In My Own Way, 1980; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - In Time, 1968; ozalid copy (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - On the Sunny Side of the Rockies, 1937 - 1938 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      Words and music also by: Harry Tobias.
    - It Didn't Come Easy, 1973; lead sheet (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - It Don't Mean A Thing, 1932; piano and voice (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - It's the Talk of the Town, 1961; piano and voice (Box 155, Folder 10)
      Lyrics also by: Al. J. Neiburg.
    - I've Still Got My Heart, Jo (Joe), ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 155, Folder 12)
      Also written by: Roger Cook, and Roger Greenaway.
    - Love Is For The Two Of Us, 1968; piano and voice (Box 157, Folder 27)
    - Jeepers Creepers, piano and voice (Box 155, Folder 16)
      Pages 3 and 4 only.
    - Eu Nao Existo Sem Voce, 1958; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Eu Sei que Vou Te Amar, 1960; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Meditation = Meditaco, 1962, 1963; piano and voice (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - The Eyes of Love, 1967; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - A Beautiful Friendship, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Le Lac Majeur = The Western Shore, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Picasso Summer, 1969; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 11)
      Plate no.: TMK-295-3
    - A Day In the Life, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      Also written by Paul McCartney. No sleeve
    - Let Go!, 1967; lead sheet; ozalid print (Box 157, Folder 1)
      Original lyrics by: Vincius De Moraes.
    - Life Song, lead sheet; ozalid print (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - El Gaucho, 1963; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 18)
      Also written by Pete Antell.
    - A Little Bit Later On, 1936; piano and voice; ozalid print (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Dirlanda, 1970; photocopied score (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Little Boat, 1962; piano and voice (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - A Perfect Paris Nightprofessional copy, 1961; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 7)
      Also composed by Hoagy Carmichael.
    - Mood Indigo, 1931; published lead sheet (Box 161, Folder 6)
      Also written by: Irving Mills and Albany Bigard.
    - Moon on My Pillow, 1942; voice, piano; photocopy (Box 161, Folder 10)
      Also written by: Elliott and Henry Tobias.
    - Moondance, 1971; voice, piano; photocopy (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - The More I See You, 1945; voice, piano (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - The more I See You, 1945; voice, piano (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Never Never Land, 1954 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      Lyrics also by: and Adolph Green.
    - Love So Fine, 1967 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Picnic, manuscript (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Pomp and Circumstance, manuscript (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Promises, Promises, 1968; rhythm; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Put Your Little Arms Around Me, 1932; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 26)
      Words and music also by: Harry Tobias, and Jules Lemare.
    - Rain and Tears, 1968 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      Plate no.: J. M. 11
    - The Loves Of July (Les Amours De Juillet), 1966 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - The Loves of July (Les Amours De Juillet), 1966 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Point It Out, 1969; manuscript (Box 166, Folder 16)
      Plate no.: Y 0160-3
      Words and music also by: Al Cleveland, and Marvin Tarplin.
    - Sail Along, Silv'ry Moon, 1937; manuscript (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Skylark, 1942; manuscript (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - So What's New?, 1966; trumpet, trombone, rhythm; manuscript, ozalid parts (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Someone to Watch Over Me, 1926; manuscript (Box 24, Folder 11)
      Plate no.: S-7854-4Fr.
    - SpellboundChappell & Co., Inc., 1945; piano and voice; copy (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Star Carol, 1954; piano and voice (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Star of Hope, 1951; piano and voice (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Sue Key Ah Kee, lead sheet; manuscript and copies (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Surfin' Beat Bull Frog, lead sheet (Box 25, Folder 23)
      *or jerk, frug, dog, monkey, twist, philly or what you will, including those not invented yet!
    - Tea for Two, 1924; manuscript (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Plate no.: S-7076-4Sp
      Lyrics also by: Johnnie Camacho.
    - Breakout, 1981; photocopied lead sheet (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Waltz, 1948; trombone; manuscript, ozalid manuscript and copies, ozalid parts (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Also written by: Pee Wee King.
    - There's No Such Thing as Love, 1963; manuscript (Box 26, Folder 17)
      Words and music also by: Anthony Newley.
    - Ooh, Ernest (Are You Earnest With Me), 1922; copied manuscript (Box 165, Folder 16)
      Words and music also by: Cliff Friend, and Sidney Clare.
    - Lost and Found, 1938; piano and voice (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Another Day, 1964; Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 26)
      Also written by Clem Watts and Herbie Herbert.
    - Far Away, 1951; manuscript (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Candida, 1970; published piano reduction (Box 77, Folder 20)
      Also written by Irwin Levine.
    - Day is Done, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - On the South Side of Chicago, 1966 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Song Lyrics, Subseries 3.
    - Assorted song lyrics (Box 169, Folder 3)
      Contains handwritten and typed copies of lyrics for various songs: After Last Night, My Woman, and Should I Give My Love Tonight.
- Artwork, undated; Series 6.
  - "The Lonely Bull" promotional print, 15 x 20" (Box 172, Folder 2)
    Matted print of Herb Alpert with caption "'The Lonely Bull' by Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass on A & M Records, Rondor Music"
  - Artwork for Herb Alpert recordings (Box 176, Folder 4)
    Record jacket for "Diamonds" 7 inch single, record jacket for "The Maltese Melody" and "Country Lake" by Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass, and transparency for label of "Rise single.
  - Record album jacket proofs (Box 176, Folder 7)
    Two album jacket proofs for Herb Alpert's Tijuana Brass: South of the Border -- Volume 2.
  - Color costume design skectches, 15.25" x 21" (Box 176, Folder 8)
    Four sketches for Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass.
  - Sketches for Tijuana Brass Fan Club materials and "The Lonely Bull" ad campaign (Box 187, Folder 7)
- Posters, 1971-1977; Series 7.
  - Showtime "Best of the Brass" poster, 16 x 11" (Box 187)
    Poster advertises Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass special "Best of the Brass" on CBS.
  - Royal Albert Hall - Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass Concert poster, 10 x 7.5" (Box 187)
    2 copies.
  - "Sounds Like" Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Poster, 14.5 x 6" (Box 187)
    Poster advertising "Sounds Like" as "on sale here!"
  - Goldener Trompetensound - Herb Alpert and The Tijuana Brass Poster, 19 x 12.5" sticker (Box 187)
    Poster advertising Herb Alpert and The Tijuana Brass in German.
  - A & M magazine advertisement., 1971 June 12; 1 pages (Box 86)
    "Our Covers" ad, from CashBox.
  - Promotional sticker, 10 stickers (Box 86)
    "Specailly priced album" sticker for "The Expression," including list of singles: "With Closed Eyes," "Nothing Changes," "Present Communication," and "Decisions."
  - A & M Records Promotional Posters, 1972; 22" x 28" ea. (Box 160)
    Box of mounted promotional posters from 1972, including these artists: Quincy Jones, Joan Baez, Burt Bacharach, Carole King, Billy Preston, Cheech and Chong, The Carpenters, Humble Pie, Herb Alpert, David T. Walker, Rita Coolideg, Merry Clayton, and Cat Stevens.
  - Catch A Star!, 28" x 44" (Box 162)
    Poster announcing an appearance by Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass featuring Lani Hall and Bobby Sandler at Harrah's South Shore Room at Tahoe.
  - Photo celebrating A & M's move into Charlie Chaplin's former home, 12" x 16", framed (Box 167, Folder 6)
    A framed poster print celebrating the new home of A & M Records while honoring it's former owner, Charlie Chaplin.
    Caption reads: Charlie Chaplin, 1889-1977; We will take care of his home with the same love, joy and integrity he gave to all of us.
  - "A & M Promo Men Do It Again" Poster, 16 x 22" (Box 172, Folder 7)
    In house joke poster. Reads "Extra, The Daily Promoter, A & M Promo Men Do It Again!!!" 3 copies.
  - In-store promotional graphic display for Herb Alpert's, "Rise." (Box 176, Folder 1)
    Three pieces. Cardboard wedge display folds to stand as in-store promotion for Herb Alpert's, "Rise."
    Includes instructions for display assembly.
  - In-store promotional photo display for Herb Alpert's, "Rise." (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Proofs of artwork advertising Herb Alpert recordings (Box 176, Folder 3)
    Two proofs: "Route One," the single from the album, "Fandango," and an advertisement for the release of the album, "My Avstract Heart."
  - Promotional display for Magic Man by Herb Alpert, 12" H (Box 176, Folder 5)
    In-store display advertising Magic Man by Herb Alpert.
  - Promotional posters for Herb Alpert albums, 10.5" x 16" (Box 176, Folder 6)
    Two promotional posters for Herb Alpert projects; one for the album, "Rise,": and one for the collaboration with Hugh Masekela.
  - Goldener Trompetensound - Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass poster., 16 x 24" (Box 184)
    Poster advertising Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass in German.
  - Herb Alpert Presents Carmine Caruso Poster, 1977 April 2; 10 x 14.5" (Box 184)
    Poster advertising Carmine Caruso concert. 4 copies.
- Clippings, 1956-1989; Series 8.
  - Herb Alpert (personal) Press Clippings, 1967-1975 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1956-1965 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1966 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1967 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, 1970-1985 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Press Clippings, Undated (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - A & M (General) Press Clippings, 1966-1989 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Suzy Isaacs Press Clippings, 1968 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Boys in the Band Press Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - A & M Performers Press Clippings, 1961-1969 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    Excludes Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass
- Awards, 1960-1987; Series 9.
  - Assorted Awards, 1960-1986; Subseries 1.
    Arranged chronologically.
    Includes citations of achievements as well as NARAS (National Association of Recorded Arts and Sciences) awards.
    - State of California, Senate Rules Committee Resolution by President pro Tempore David Roberti; relative to commending Herb Alpert.., 1986 May 30 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      Senate Rules Committee Resolution No. 1874, that Herb Alpert be extended the special honors and commendations of the people of California for his exemplary musical talent and ability, his business acumen, and his many community contributions.
    - What a Wonderful World Broadcast Music, Inc. Certificates of Million-Performance Status (Box 149, Folder 2-3)
    - To Herb Alpert, from the President of Puerto Rico, celebrating 27 years, 17" x 6", plaque (Box 167, Folder 1)
      On plaque: Por sus 27 anos en la musica instrumental en todos los tiempos. Ayer, hoy y siempre.
    - United States Commander Berlin recognizes Herbert Alpert, A Guardian of Berlin's Freedom, 1966 October 1; 12.5" x 17.5", framed (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Herb Alpert, an Honorary Citizen of New Orleans, 1977 August 8 (Box 168, Folder 18)
      Certificate presented by the Mayor and members of City Council, New Orleans.
    - Certificate of Dedication to Herb Alpert, for the Cities in Schools Sub-School at Jordan L. Mott Junior High School., 1979 October 15 (Box 168, Folder 19)
      Certificate for the dedication of the Cities in Schools Sub-School at Jordan L. Mott Junior High School in the New York City Public Schools District 9, as The Herb Alpert Sub School.
    - City of Los Angeles Commendation presented to Herb Alpert., 1987 November 18 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      Commendation from Tom Bradley, Mayor of the City of Los Angeles, extends congratulations and best wishes for continued success.
    - Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Irving Music, Inc., 1968 (Box 168, Folder 21)
      Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Herb Alpert for "Classical Gas."
    - Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Irving Music, Inc., 1968 (Box 168, Folder 22)
      Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Herb Alpert for "Carmen."
    - BMI Citation of Acievement to Irving Music, Inc. for "Windy.", 1968; 12.5" x 18" (Box 168, Folder 23)
      Certificate reads: in recognition of great national popularity, as measured by broadcast performances, attained by Windy.
    - Three Citations of Achievement to Herb Alpert for "Wonderful World.", 12" x 16" (Box 168, Folder 24)
      Each citation reads: "in recognition of the great national popularity .. attained by 'Wonderful World'."
    - Herb Alpert Day, Metropolitan Dade County, Florida., 1974 November 19; 15" x 18" (Box 168, Folder 25)
      Proclamation by Stephen P. Clark, Mayor of Metropolitan Dade County, Florida, celebrating Tuesday, November 19, 1974, as Herb Alpert Day.
    - NARAS certificate presented to producers Herb Alpert and Randy Badazz for the Best Pop Instrumental Performance of the Year, "Rise.", 1979; 16" x 20" (Box 168, Folder 29)
    - American Mexican Institute of Cultural Exchange Good Neighbor Award to Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass, 1965 September (Box 168, Folder 30)
    - Billboard Top LP's Herb Alpert #1 in the Nation plaque, 1966 April 16 (Box 168, Folder 31)
    - Cash Box A&M records plaque, 1966 September 17 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Herb Alpert and Tijuana Brass Honorary Citizen of New Orleans framed certificate, 1966 February 26 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - County of Los Angeles Commends Herb Alpert for His Dedicated Community Service, 1986 June 13; 12.5 x 21.5" (Box 172, Folder 5)
      Certificate in folder, presented to Herb Alpert by the County of Los Angeles in commendation of his dedicated community service and honor given by The City of Hope.
    - Resolution by the City of Los Angeles honoring Herb Alpert and Jerome Sheldon Moss for their contributions to the Los Angles Free Clinic, December 9, 1988; 13 x 22" (Box 172, Folder 6)
      Certificate in folder, presented to Herb Alpert and Jerry Moss for their contributions to the Los Angeles Free Clinic.
    - Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Herb Alpert., 1960 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      Citation of Achievement presented by Broadcast Music, Inc., to Herb Alpert for "Wonderful World."
    - Tijuana Brass Certificate for Herb Alpert from the city of Tijuana, Baja California, Mexico, 1966 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences (NARAS) certificate presented to Herb Alpert's Tijuana Brass for "Whipped Cream & Other Delights", 1965; plaque (Box 151)
      Certificate presnted to Herb Alpert's Tijuana Brass in recognition of Nomination for the Album of the Year, "Whipped Cream & Other Delights."
    - The Concert for Bangla Desh, 1971 August 1 (Box 150)
      Presented to A & M Records in gratitude for cooperation and assistance in the production of the concert for Bangla Desh.
    - The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences (NARAS) certificate presented to Herb Alpert, 1983 (Box 152)
      Certificate presented to Herb Alpert in recognition of Nomination for the Best Pop Instrumental Performance, "Blow Your Own Horn," Album.
    - State of California, Senate Rules Committee Resolution by President pro Tempore David Roberti; relative to commending Herb Alpert.., 1986 May 30 (Box 149)
  - Grammy Awards Souvenir Scrapbooks, 1987 February 24; Subseries 2.; 4 items
    Guest books filled with hundreds of pages of greetings and signatures.
    - A & M Annual Grammy Celebration Party, 1987 February 24
      A guest book with hundreds of pages of greetings and signatures. Paper-bound.
    - A & M Annual Grammy Celebration Party, 1987 February 24
    - A & M Annual Grammy Celebration Party, 1987 February 24
      A guest book with hundreds of pages of greetings and signatures. Most of the pages in this leather-bound volume are empty.
    - A & M Annual Grammy Celebration Party, February 24, 1987, 1987 February 24 (Box 153)
    - A & M Annual Grammy Celebration Party, February 24, 1987, 1987 February 24 (Box 154)
  - Platinum and Gold Records, Subseries 3.; 62 items
    Arranged alphabetically by recipient.
    Gold and platinum records presented to various A & M artists including Herb Alpert, Joan Baez, Carole King, Sting and Yes.
    - Bryan Adams, "Into the Fire," award presented to Herb Alpert (Box 89)
      Presented by Canyon Records, Inc., for Bryan Adams, "Into the Fire."
      For significant sales in Japan.
    - Bryan Adams, "Into the Fire," award presented to Herb Alpert (Box 90)
    - "A Very Special Christmas," Platinum Album presented to Herb Alpert, Framed platinum album, ca. 17"x22" (Box 86)
      Certified RIAA sales award for "A Very Special Christmas."
      Platinum Record: More than one million copies, album and cassette, sold.
    - "A Very Special Christmas," Platinum Album presented to Herb Alpert (Box 87)
      Platinum Disc Award presented by Pony Canyon, Inc., for "A Very Special Christmas."
      150,000 units sold (in Japan)
    - A & M Records Honorary RIAA Gold Record. Presented, one to Herb Alpert, one to Jerry Moss, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 88)
      Certified RIAA sales award for the 25th Anniversary of A & M Records - 1962-1987. 2 copies.
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Warm," Gold Album presented to Herb Alpert, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 91)
      Certified RIAA sales award for Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Warm."
      Gold Album: More than one million dollars worth of the LP record album sold.
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "America," Gold Album (Box 92)
      Gold Album
      25,000 copies sold in Sweden during August 1969
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "S.R.O.," Gold Record presented to Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, 1967 April; Gold record on Plaque. 14" x 17" (Box 94)
      Australian Gold Record Award presented by Festival Records, Australia - New Zealand.
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "S.R.O.," Gold Record presented to Herb Alpert, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 95)
      Certified RIAA sales award for Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "S.R.O."
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Herb Alpert's Ninth," Gold Album presented to Herb Alpert, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 97)
      Certified RIAA sales award for Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Herb Alpert's Ninth."
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Sounds Like," Gold Album presented to Herb Alpert, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 98)
      Certified RIAA sales award for Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "Sounds Like."
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "The Lonely Bull," Gold Album presented to Herb Alpert, Framed gold album. ca. 17"x22" (Box 99)
      Certified RIAA sales award for Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, "The Lonely Bull."